
You need to implement the following functionality:

1.Re-design your system to support different user roles, e.g. Student, Trainer, Head Master. The  user  must  be  able  to  login  to  the  system with  these different roles

2.Each role should be able to do specific actions as these are designated by the Head Master,
a.Student,enroll  to  any Course  under  any Trainerand  submit  any Assignments that are designated to him / her
b.Trainer,  view  the  list  of  the  Students  and  mark  any  assignments
c.Head  Master, create  any  courses  needed,  appoint  the  trainer(s) and the students under each of the courses, appoint assignments to each of the courses

3.The login  system  must  implement  persistence  and  securityalong  with password hashing.
 
Specifically,each role must be ableto do the following:

a.Student
i.See his / herdaily Scheduleper Course
ii.See the dates of submission of the Assignments per Course
iii.Submit any Assignments

b.Trainer
i.View alltheCourses he / she is enrolled 
ii.View all the Students per Course
iii.View all the Assignments per Student per Course
iv.Mark all the Assignments per Student per Coursec.

Head Master
i.CRUD on Courses
ii.CRUD on Students
iii.CRUD on Assignments
iv.CRUD on Trainers
v.CRUD on Students per Courses
vi.CRUD on Trainers per Courses
vii.CRUD on Assignments per Courses
viii.CRUD on Schedule per Courses